clickcash.com 2012-12-26

# ClickCash - Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Effective: March 2009**

ClickCash.com respects and safeguards the privacy of every individual who visits our website. This Privacy Policy is a formal document that outlines the information which may be collected about you while you use ClickCash.com, and how that information may be used. This Policy will also instruct you on what to do if you do not want your personally-identifiable information collected or shared when you visit ClickCash.com. 

**Personally-Identifiable Information**

ClickCash.com collects your personally-identifiable information (including, but not limited to, your name, your business name, address, telephone number, email address, social security number, business identification number, financial information, or any combination of data that could be used to identify you, such as birth date and zip code) when you voluntarily provide it to us or authorize our access to it. Your personally-identifiable information will be used to verify your age and identity, as well as to provide you with support services while you are using ClickCash.com (a third-party service may be used to validate your age and identification information). Financial information that is collected is used to check your qualifications for registration and to ensure proper payment for products and services. Additional third parties who provide support services on our behalf, such as banking services, electronic payment services, email delivery services, and other professional services may have limited access to your personally-identifiable information in order to provide their services. Any third-party service provider that we authorize to access or use your personally-identifiable information will not use your information for other purposes beyond providing the service. We do not share, sell, rent, or trade your personally-identifiable information with any third parties for their promotional purposes. 

We may use your personally-identifiable information in the following ways: we may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services; and we may use that information to contact you about billing issues, technical issues, or as a follow-up to your request to receive more information about our products and services. By using ClickCash.com, you expressly authorize us to disclose your personally-identifiable information if we have a good faith belief that the access, use, preservation, or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request; enforce applicable Terms of Service, including the investigation of potential violations thereof; detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; or protect against harm to the rights, property, or safety of WebPower, Inc., its users, or the public as required or permitted by law. In your capacity as both the sender and the recipient of electronic communications on or through WebPower’s services, you expressly agree and authorize us to access your personally-identifiable information and to disclose your personally-identifiable information to government agencies pursuant to valid legal procedures; this authorization relates to the personally-identifiable information that you distribute on or through ClickCash.com as well as to the personally-identifiable information that you store on ClickCash.com. 

If you provide your personally-identifiable information to us in reference to a domain name that you become aware of on or through ClickCash.com, we will share such personally-identifiable information with the domain name seller in order to provide the domain name seller with information to contact you directly and independently; we will not otherwise share such information with third parties, except as stated in this policy. 

Your use of ClickCash.com may also include the transfer of your personally-identifiable information, individual information, personal data and/or sensitive information outside of your country, including without limitation from the European Union to the United States. At all times, you have the right and ability to withhold the transfer of your personally-identifiable information, individual information, personal data and/or sensitive information by not establishing an account with this service. You agree that the transfer of such information is necessary to establish a ClickCash.com Associate relationship with WebPower, Inc., and by establishing an account with ClickCash.com you provide express voluntary consent for your personally-identifiable information, individual information, personal data and/or sensitive information to be transferred and processed outside of your country, including without limitation from the European Union to the United States. 

If your personally-identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire to use ClickCash.com, you may update or deactivate your information by emailing us at [acctupdate @ clickcash](mailto:acctupdate@clickcash.com), or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail using the contact information listed at the bottom of this page. 

**Non-Personally-Identifiable Information Collected Automatically**

In some cases, information that is not personally-identifiable may be automatically collected about you either through server log files or cookies (examples of this type of information include without limitation your IP address, the type of internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site). For registered users of WebPower, Inc.'s web properties, we link this information to your account information; however, for non-registered users, we never link this information to any personally-identifiable information. 

**Information That May Be Placed Automatically On Your Computer's Hard Drive**

When you view our websites, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor web pages to better match your interests and preferences, and maintain your login session. For registered users of our web properties, we link this information to your account information; however, for non-registered users, we never link this information to any personally-identifiable information. With most internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. To learn how to prevent ClickCash.com from using cookies during your visit to ClickCash.com and/or our other web properties, and how to erase cookies from your hard drive, see our [Guide to Managing Cookies](http://www.clickcash.com/ifpage.dll?t=ALT/clickcash/general/ManageCookies). 

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can email us at [security @ clickcash](mailto:security@clickcash.com). 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and at other places we deem appropriate. 

**Who to Contact**

You may receive email communications related to the support services that ClickCash.com provides to you. You may opt out of such email communications at any time by contacting [support @ clickcash](mailto:support@clickcash.com) and discontinuing your use of the ClickCash.com services. 

If you have submitted personally-identifiable information through the ClickCash.com website and would like that information removed from our records, please contact our ClickCash Support Team at [support @ clickcash](mailto:support@clickcash.com) and provide us with your name, your ClickCash.com account name, and any information you feel is important. We will use reasonable efforts to remove this information from our existing files. 

If you have further questions about this Privacy Policy: 

• Contact us at our email address: [support @ clickcash](mailto:support@clickcash.com)

• Contact us at our toll-free telephone number: 1-800-243-9726, ext. 670 

• Contact us at our postal address:

Attention: Privacy Department - ClickCash  
3395 S. Jones Blvd., Suite 22  
Las Vegas, NV 89146 USA
